Tada! Hello everyone. Welcome back to
the Peace of Alice channel. Yes, the
rumors are true. It is the day after my
birthday and yes, the rumors are true
part two, I am 24 years old.
When I say it's the day after my
birthday, what I actually mean is it's
two days after my birthday, but
yesterday just doesn't count cuz I was
so hung over, couldn't leave my bed. Um
so we're just we're just going to
pretend that day never happened. So
today instead, I'm going to go birthday
shopping. I'm so excited. I have not
been shopping in a minute and my family
was nice enough to give me a little bit
of money. So I'm going to go and spend
that today. Guys, also this is just a
regular girls birthday haul. I feel like
on this platform there's a lot of, you
know, I see these influencers going
shopping for their birthday and it's
like they're hitting Chanel, they're
hitting like Vivienne Westwood. It's
super fun to watch, but it's just like
that's that's not me. So I thought, you
know what, let me take you guys on a
normal girl birthday shopping haul as
someone who is one on a budget and two,
rather financially responsible. Anyway,
my mom's free today. So I'm bringing her
along with me. Guys, this is me and my
mom shopping for my birthday. Let's go.
Guys, I'm with my mom. Say hi, mom.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, we're matching with the glasses.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Mom, are you excited to be going
shopping with me today?
>> wait.
So excited to see what you're going to
buy me.
>> [laughter]
>> My phone case literally matches my top
perfectly.
>> [music]
>> Okay, we're on Oxford Street. First
stop, we're going to go to Primark
because there's some pajamas that I want
to get.
>> [music]
>> My mom's duty is to locate these pajamas
because you're really good at finding
stuff.
>> Wait, Snoopy with the pumpkin is
actually really cute.
>> The material is nicer.
>> That is nice actually. But no, I'm
looking for Rilakkuma. You know the bear
that I like, the brown bear that I was
showing you.
We we will find it, I'm sure. Oh wait,
look, there's a Yes, one of them's here.
That's cute.
No, actually, I hate it. But there
should be other ones. Oh wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, I found
it. I found it.
And look, this one as well. Look.
>> Oh, that's cute.
>> Yeah, right? I think I'm going to get
these.
The socks, wow.
I kind of feel like the big t-shirt.
Wow, this is a really big t-shirt.
>> That's a really big t-shirt.
>> Hold this, hold this here.
>> [laughter]
>> Is the one I wanted.
Okay, but first, coffee. £14, I actually
feel like that's quite expensive for
Primark. That's kind of annoyed me. Do
you know what I mean? But this is just
so my vibes right now.
>> Yeah.
>> Right?
>> You could literally wear it as a dress.
I would.
Yeah, I would.
>> Yeah, cuz this is looking
>> Check check the bottoms there.
Oh my god, they're cute. Look at that
bear.
That bear's cute.
>> Oh, that is really cute. I'm going to
get the socks 6 to 8 cuz I've got big
feet.
>> Oh my god, I've to actually take them
off.
>> That's my fault for having big feet.
Actually, it's your fault for giving
birth to me with big feet.
>> I'm sorry.
>> Look, they have Essence. Mom, honestly,
I'm not joking. You need to get one of
these mascaras. They're really cheap and
they're really good.
You're always like Look, it's like £3,
£2.30. Honestly, Essence is like Essence
is really good. Oh, I'm getting I need a
new lip balm, so I'm going to get a lip
balm.
Super glossy lip treatment.
Well, I'll get it for you if you want.
Cuz it's £3.30 and it's good and it's
here. Do you know what I mean? Is this
like a red
burgundy mascara? Wait, I really like
burgundy mascara. Yeah, I used to wear
it all the time last autumn. And I
remember you used to tell me it was
really nice.
>> Yeah, get one place then.
>> Oh, what's this? Bouncy jelly. What's
this stuff called? Bouncy jelly.
>> 3.50.
>> No, I don't like it. It looks I don't
like it.
>> It is fizzy sherbet.
>> No, I don't like it.
>> to smell it though.
>> All right.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, smell that.
Oh, it's fizzy sherbet.
>> put it on my lip, Mom.
I'm going to get like poisoned.
>> [laughter]
>> Now we're going to my favorite
bookstore. My mom also loves this
bookstore because I realized I don't
have any books that I haven't read right
now. I literally last night I went to go
and read a book. Babes, they're all
finished. So, you know, I'm about to
scout out a new one today. Maybe a
cheeky little manga as well. Are you
going to look for a book, Mom?
>> I might have to treat myself even I've
got a
>> Go on. 300 that still haven't read.
>> Or do you want to eat first?
>> What do you want to do?
>> Maybe cuz maybe cuz we're here, let's
eat first.
>> [music]
>> Right, off to food break. How are you
feeling now, Mom? Rejuvenated for more
shopping?
>> Yeah.
>> Yay.
>> [laughter]
>> That's not true.
>> No, I hate shopping.
>> It's just the the biggest lie you've
told.
>> I'm prepared to uh
>> Yay.
We're here.
Let's go.
Oh, they reopened the cafe. It was like
closed the last time I was here.
>> I love her.
>> You picking up a book straight away.
>> Yeah, look.
>> [laughter]
>> Of course I love her.
>> [music]
>> This is right up my street. It's like a
romance about like a ghost and like a
human, I think.
From what I can gauge.
>> [laughter]
>> Perfect. Mom, what would you do if I
told you I was in a relationship with a
ghost?
>> I wouldn't be surprised.
>> Yay, manga section. Domo.
Oh my god, Domo. Oh, look. Nana, my
fave.
I've been wanting to get the anniversary
edition.
Purely because it's cute.
But like I've got all of the volumes, so
I just don't need it.
This is cute.
Why is there straight cats playing in
this bookstore? Where is it coming from?
This is so cute. They opened a new bar
in here.
>> No.
>> You don't remember when I got accepted
into uni, but I I already told everyone
I didn't want to go and then Nan told
everyone, "Oh, my granddaughter got is
going to uni."
>> I have no recollection [laughter] of
that.
>> You don't remember? Anyway, I saw that
this um cafe online does this drink
where it's like a split. Mom, listen to
this. So, it's like a cup, right? But
the cup is like split in half. It's half
matcha and half coffee.
>> Oh, you told me [clears throat] about
this.
>> Yeah, so like but it's so good for me
cuz I can't decide. No, I never had it,
but I really wanted to try it, so.
That is so cute.
>> I think we're meant to Wiggles Live at
some point.
>> Oh, Mom.
>> But it's okay. It's all in this
direction and then over there.
>> Are you sure about that?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, no nice nice fan in the
background.
>> Yeah, it's cute, isn't it?
>> Yeah.
Oh, look at the eyes on the fan.
Ew.
I love this area. You know
>> You might just see a little bit
of a pan of the nice
Oh look, it's like a little play park or
something.
Is it a play park? No, it probably
isn't, is it?
And wildlife, but I just don't think
there's any wildlife in Holborn.
Actually, it's not that nice when you
get closer.
>> [laughter]
>> Is it?
The coffee arrived. Oh my god, look at
the latte. Oh, they did for my mom. Oh
my god. They knew we were cat people.
How did they know? How did they know?
And then
>> [laughter]
>> this is killing me.
It is giving what's it, but this is my
ice banana latte. Yes, I changed my mind
last minute. I love banana. So it does
it. It's actually banana pudding latte.
>> [music]
>> Guys, I really recommend [music] you
come here.
And try the banana pudding at latte. I'm
not
>> [music]
>> playing with you. Wow, that coffee.
I feel rejuvenated. Mom, rate your
coffee out of 10.
>> 10.
>> Oh.
>> Yeah, with the cat, 11.
>> She's feeling generous today. I'm taking
my mom to the anime store.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, we'll see what's going on in
Forbidden Planet. I do love Forbidden
Planet.
>> Way back to back my dad also loved
Forbidden Planet.
>> Really? Oh yeah, he did, didn't he?
>> Sci-fi fan.
>> He's a bit of a nerd, wasn't he?
>> Yeah.
>> Well, yeah. And now I've got the nerd
gene, so.
>> First first sorry.
>> [music]
>> Oh my god, she's so cute.
>> Oh, it's cuz you sit her on the side of
like a
>> You sit her on the side of a mug.
This is so cute. Sanrio Town. Oh my god,
why have they got spooky cinnamon roll?
That's really cute.
Just left a bit of Plan It. Shout out to
the cashier, she was so cute. Forgot to
ask for her name. But if you're watching
this, you know who you are. Anyway, I
got a little Sonny Angel. I got the
flower series. I just missed the series
that I wanted to get. She told me they
sold out. Don't worry, girl, I'll be
back. Anyway, we're going to unbox this.
Haul time. So, let's get into the
birthday shopping haul. I got the PJ
set. Yes, I did. I got this one because
it Guys, I don't care. I feel like a lot
of people would have thought this is the
ugliest one, but I just think it gives
like 2012, like derp. Like I just love
it. Like okay, but first coffee. It's so
2012 Tumblr millennial core. And I just
Guys, I love it. Like And the boxer
shorts are so cute. And guys, I'm
actually going to change into this right
now.
I absolutely love it.
>> [laughter]
>> Like why is it the cutest thing ever?
I'm feeling so derp right now. I love
it. Okay, and then I got the socks.
These are so cute and they were only
2.50. Great because I just I'm I always
need socks. Like where do they go? Where
do they go? I feel like there's like a
void in my room where socks just
disappear to. This is the first design.
And then this is the second design. And
then the third one is Keroppi. So cute.
I literally love him so much. So more
essentials, just got some underwear. You
know, while I was there, needed to be
bought. The colors are so cute though.
And then yeah, they had a Essence makeup
section in Primark and it's so cheap and
affordable. So I actually I bought my
mom a mascara because this is my
favorite mascara and I recommend this to
everyone. It's so affordable and I wear
this all the time. Anyways, yeah, they
had a burgundy version. So I bought the
burgundy version for myself cuz in
autumn, a little burgundy mascara
moment, I love it. Next up, I bought
from Essence as well. Peptide super
glossy lip treatment. I've never tried
this, but I just run out of my current
like lip balm that I use. I've got a
million lip glosses, not a single lip
balm. That's almost comedic.
Ooh.
Oh, I didn't know it was going to be
pigmented cuz I was going to wear this
before bed. I will just be going to bed
with a pink lip. I don't mind. Next up,
we went to the bookstore, which also I
can't believe they've opened up a bar in
my favorite bookstore. Are you joking?
Do you want me to move in? Cuz now
you've got a cafe, a cocktail bar, a
record store, a stationery store, manga,
and like regular books. Do you want me
to move in? Like that's all of my
favorite things in one place. Like I
feel like a dog hearing the word walk
and treat in the same sentence. Like
that's my vibe right now. Anyway, so I
picked up two books from the
Waterstones. First one is called
Swallowed. Swallowed. A bit difficult to
read title, but it sounded very
interesting. A dystopian fantasy. I got
another book, too. This is I in the
Shadows. It's like a I think it's like a
supernatural ghost love story. There's a
ghost haunting this girl's room. I think
she falls in love with him. A bit crazy,
but you know what? I get it. So yeah, I
picked up those two books and they're
not too long, so I'll probably plow
through these. Then I got a manga. Once
again, I've just read everything that
I'm interested in until I saw this and I
thought first of all, the art style is
super cute. Like I saw this cover and I
was like, wait, she's adorable. It's one
of the like one-off mangas that isn't
like multiple volumes and I like those
from time to time, you know? Like it
gives read it in one sitting. Yeah, it's
kind of it kind of gives the vibe of
like My Neighbor Totoro slash Spirited
Away, you know? Like girl moves to a
small town. She's like a little kid. She
left the city, left her friends, and
then she's like being drawn to like the
ocean and stuff and there's like a
mermaid and like all of this. Anyway,
sounds super cute and the art style
looks cute, too.
Final thing that I bought in my birthday
haul, a Sonny Angel. Obviously, I had to
buy a Sonny Angel for my birthday. I
feel like these days I don't buy blind
boxes anymore because it feels like I
don't want to say waste of money because
guys, it's never a waste of money. Like
don't believe me. Like believe me, it's
never a waste of money. Like but what I
mean by that is like I have like many
from years ago. I can't justify buying
more unless it's a special occasion such
as my birthday. But I have a tradition
now of buying myself a Sonny Angel every
birthday. That's the only time I will
allow myself. Otherwise, I will just
fall back into addiction.
Let's unbox this little guy. I got the
flower gift series.
I'm going to close my eyes.
This is an interesting shape.
Oh!
Oh my gosh! This is adorable.
Oh, and then I also have to show you
what my friend got me because I can't
get over this gift. Guys, she got me a
Crocs handbag. Are you kidding me?
It's so cute. Obviously, I need to get
some gibbets. And I do need to get the
Crocs in the matching color. Like not
being funny. That was my birthday haul.
Very fun day celebrating my birthday.
I'm so grateful to my friends and
family. I feel so happy this year to
turn 24. More than any other year, I
think. I say that every year, but I just
feel so grateful. It's been an amazing
year. Thank you guys for being there
with me this year. And I hope we make
more memories together in the upcoming
years. Thank you so much for watching,
guys. I'll see you in the next video.